Guide to the University of Chicago Department of Botany Records 1882-1972
University of Chicago Library
- Series VI: Photographs, circa 1891-1936
  - Subseries 7: Lantern Slides
    - Hawaii, AEP-HIS2, Ohia on the Chain of Craters Road, Hawaii Volcanoes National Park, Hawaii AEP-HIS3, Astelia on the Chain of Craters Road, Hawaii Volcanoes National Park, Hawaii AEP-HIS4, Coprosma sp. on the Chain of Craters Road, Hawaii Volcanoes National Park, Hawaii AEP-HIS5, False Stag Horn Fern on the Chain of Craters Road, Hawaii Volcanoes National Park, Hawaii AEP-HIS6, Sadleria and lichens on the Chain of Craters Road, Hawaii Volcanoes National Park, Hawaii AEP-HIS7, Plant roots seen through lava, Chain of Craters Road, Hawaii Volcanoes National Park, Hawaii AEP-HIS8, Eye of the Eel, Chain of Craters Road, Hawaii Volcanoes National Park, Hawaii AEP-HIS9, On the Chain of Craters Road, Hawaii Volcanoes National Park, Hawaii AEP-HIS10, City of Refuge National Historical Park, Hawaii AEP-HIS11, Pandanus, Hilo, Hawaii AEP-HIS12, Pandanus near Hilo, Hawaii AEP-HIS13, A worker carrying Sugar Cane, Hilo, Hawaii AEP-HIS14, Sugar Cane fluming, Hilo, Hawaii AEP-HIS15, Sugar Cane fluming, Hilo, Hawaii AEP-HIS16, A Sugar Cane irrigation flume near Hilo, Hawaii AEP-HIS17, Palms at Hookena, Hawaii AEP-HIS18, Palms at Hookena, Hawaii AEP-HIS19, Palms at Hookena, Hawaii AEP-HIS20, Palms at Hookena, Hawaii AEP-HIS21, Palms at Hookena, Hawaii AEP-HIS22, Climbing Screw Pine, Kalapana, Hawaii AEP-HIS23, Climbing Screw Pine, Kalapana, Hawaii AEP-HIS24, Kanenelu Bay, Hawaii AEP-HIS25, Panicum growing over Tree Fern, Keaau, Hawaii AEP-HIS26, Ohia growing on the truck of a Tree Fern, Kilauea, Hawaii AEP-HIS27, Tree Fern, Kilauea, Hawaii AEP-HIS28, A Fern forest, Kilauea, Hawaii AEP-HIS29, A Fern forest at the edge of the Kilauea Crater, Hawaii AEP-HIS30, The flow of 1868, Crater of Kilauea, Hawaii AEP-HIS31, Kilauea Crater, Volcano House, Hawaii AEP-HIS32, Kilauea, Hawaii AEP-HIS33, A sulphur bank, Kilauea Crater, Hawaii AEP-HIS34, Bird Park, Kilauea, Hawaii AEP-HIS35, Bird Park, Kilauea, Hawaii AEP-HIS36, Bird Park, Kilauea, Hawaii AEP-HIS37, Bird Park in the rain, Kilauea, Hawaii AEP-HIS38, Bird Park, Kilauea, Hawaii AEP-HIS39, A Sugar Cane field, Kohala, Hawaii AEP-HIS40, Mesquite at Kona, Hawaii AEP-HIS41, A lava flow, Kona, Hawaii AEP-HIS42, Coffee blossoms, Kona, Hawaii AEP-HIS43, Coffee growing at Kona, Hawaii AEP-HIS44, Drying Coffee, Kona, Hawaii AEP-HIS45, Coffee plantation, Kona, Hawaii AEP-HIS46, Coffee plantation, Kona, Hawaii AEP-HIS47, Coffee pickers at Kona, Hawaii AEP-HIS48, A view of Kona, Hawaii AEP-HIS49, A view of Kona, Hawaii AEP-HIS50, A view of Kona, Hawaii AEP-HIS51, A view of Kona, Hawaii AEP-HIS52, A view of Kona, Hawaii AEP-HIS53, A Native Hawaiian, Kona, Hawaii AEP-HIS54, Oha at Kukuihaele, Hawaii AEP-HIS55, A Sugar Cane flume, Kukuihaele, Hawaii AEP-HIS56, Opuntia, Mamalahoa Highway, Hawaii AEP-HIS57, Opuntia, Mamalahoa Highway, Hawaii AEP-HIS58, Seedling Opuntia, Mamalahoa Highway, Hawaii AEP-HIS59, The volcano Mauna Kea from the north, Hawaii AEP-HIS60, The volcano Mauna Kea from the Parker Ranch, Hawaii AEP-HIS61, The volcano Mauna Loa, Volcano House, Hawaii AEP-HIS62, A Sugar Cane field at Niulii, Hawaii AEP-HIS63, A Sugar Cane flume, Niulii, Hawaii AEP-HIS64, Climbing Screw Pine near Pahoa, Hawaii AEP-HIS65, Edge of a Sugar Cane field, Pahoa, Hawaii AEP-HIS66, An Ohia which started on the trunk of a now dead Tree Fern, Volcano House, Hawaii AEP-HIS67, An Ohia which started on the trunk of a Tree Fern, Volcano House, Hawaii AEP-HIS68, Volcano House, Hawaii AEP-HIS69, Volcano House, Hawaii AEP-HIS70, Lycopodium gametophytes near a sulfur steam pit, Volcano House, Hawaii AEP-HIS71, Lycopodium gametophytes near a sulfur steam pit, Volcano House, Hawaii AEP-HIS72, Lycopodium gametophytes near a sulfur steam pit, Volcano House, Hawaii AEP-HIS73, A view of Bird Park, Volcano House, Hawaii AEP-HIS74, A view of Bird Park, Volcano House, Hawaii AEP-HIS75, A view of Bird Park, Volcano House, Hawaii AEP-HIS76, Dodder at Waiohinu, Hawaii AEP-HIS77, Dodder at Waiohinu, Hawaii AEP-HIS78, Waiohinu, Hawaii AEP-HIS79, Waiohinu, Hawaii AEP-HIS80, Sisal growing on the island of Hawaii AEP-HIS86, The lava flow of 1886 on the island of Hawaii AEP-HIS87, The lava flow of 1886 on the island of Hawaii AEP-HIS89, Edge of the 1907 lava flow on the island of Hawaii AEP-HIS90, Edge of the 1907 lava flow on the island of Hawaii AEP-HIS91, Lava flow of 1886 on the island of Hawaii AEP-HIS92, Edge of two flows from 1887 and 1907 on the island of Hawaii AEP-HIS94, Northeast coast of the island of Hawaii AEP-HIS95, Northeast coast of the island of Hawaii AEP-HIS96, Northeast coast of the island of Hawaii AEP-HIS97, Sugar Cane cutting on the island of Hawaii AEP-HIS98, Bagged Sugar Cane "seed" in the field on the island of Hawaii AEP-HIS99, Sugar Cane on the island of Hawaii AEP-HIS100, Fish nets on the island of Hawaii AEP-HIS101, Making Pandanus mats on the island of Hawaii AEP-HIS102, A view across a valley showing almost complete erosion, Anahola, Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS103, Field of Pineapple, Anahola, Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS104, Barking Sands, island of Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS105, Barking Sands, island of Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS106, Barking Sands, island of Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS107, Barking Sands, island of Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS108, Barking Sands, island of Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS109, Hanalei, Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS110, Hanalei, Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS111, Hanalei, Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS112, Hanalei, Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS113, Near Hanalei, Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS114, Hanalei Valley, Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS115, Hanamaulu Bay, Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS116, Hanapepe Canyon, Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS117, Hanapepe Canyon, Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS118, A drainage ditch on land recovered for Sugar Cane, Kekaha, Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS120, Showing erosion remnants near Lihue Airport, Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS121, Picking up the Sugar cane harvest, island of Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS122, Laying track through the harvested Sugar Cane, island of Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS123, Mesquite, Makaweli, Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS124, Field of Sugar Cane, Makaweli, Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS125, Nawiliwili Bay, Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS126, Nawiliwili Bay, Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS127, Port Allen, Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS128, Port Allen, Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS129, Waialeale, Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS130, Waialeale seen from homesteads, Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS131, Looking toward Waialeale, Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS132, Coconut Palms on a plantation, Wailua, Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS133, Waimea, Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS134, Waimea Canyon, Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS135, Waimea Canyon, Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS136, The Wainiha Valley, Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS137, Near Wainiha, Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS138, Coconuts sprouting, island of Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS139, Kiawe, island of Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS140, Island of Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS141, The burning of Sugar Cane before cutting, island of Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS142, Sugar Cane cut for "seed," island of Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS143, Sugar Cane cutting, island of Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS144, Sugar Cane harvest, island of Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS145, Using nitrate fertilizer in irrigation water on Sugar Cane, island of Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS146, Rails in a Sugar Cane field, island of Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS147, Sugar Cane, island of Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS148, A Sugar Cane field, island of Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS149, A Sugar Cane field, island of Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS150, A Pineapple field, island of Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS151, Rice fields, island of Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS152, Rice fields, island of Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS153, Sugar Cane, island of Maui, Hawaii AEP-HIS154, A native house and yard, island of Kauai, Hawaii AEP-HIS155, A Sugar Cane field, island of Maui, Hawaii AEP-HIS156, Sugar Cane burning before the harvest, island of Maui, Hawaii AEP-HIS157, Sugar Cane trash burning, island of Maui, Hawaii AEP-HIS158, Sugar Cane trash before burning, island of Maui, Hawaii AEP-HIS159, Sugar Cane trash after burning, island of Maui, Hawaii AEP-HIS160, Sugar Cane trash being brought into the fields, island of Maui, Hawaii AEP-HIS161, Workers covering Sugar Cane "seed," island of Maui, Hawaii AEP-HIS162, A woman planting Sugar Cane "seed," island of Maui, Hawaii AEP-HIS163, The irrigation of Sugar Cane after planting, island of Maui, Hawaii AEP-HIS164, A Sugar Cane harvest, island of Maui, Hawaii AEP-HIS165, Sugar Cane in stony ground, island of Maui, Hawaii AEP-HIS166, Sugar Cane in stony ground, island of Maui, Hawaii AEP-HIS167, Sugar Cane molasses cars, island of Maui, Hawaii AEP-HIS168, Sugar Cane molasses car, island of Maui, Hawaii AEP-HIS169, An engine for plowing, island of Maui, Hawaii AEP-HIS171, The windward side of the island of Molokai, Hawaii AEP-HIS172, A Sugar Cane station, island of Molokai, Hawaii AEP-HIS173, Hawaiian Sugar Planters Association quarantine house, island of Molokai, Hawaii AEP-HIS174, Hawaiian Sugar Planters Association quarantine station, island of Molokai, Hawaii AEP-HIS175, Hawaiian Sugar Planters Association quarantine station, island of Molokai, Hawaii AEP-HIS176, Hawaiian Sugar Planters Association quarantine station, island of Molokai, Hawaii AEP-HIS177, Hawaiian Sugar Planters Association quarantine houses, island of Molokai, Hawaii AEP-HIS178, Taking a shower on the island of Molokai, Hawaii AEP-HIS179, Diamond Head, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS180, Diamond Head, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS181, Diamond Head, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS182, Diamond Head, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS183, Diamond Head, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS184, Diamond Head, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS185, Sugar Cane growing at Ewa-Schofield Junction, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS186, Ewa-Schofield Junction, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS187, Ewa-Schofield Junction, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS188, Ewa-Schofield Junction, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS189, Haleiwa, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS190, Haleiwa, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS191, Near Hanauma Bay, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS192, Near Hanauma Bay, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS193, Araucaria bidwillii, Honolulu, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS194, Banyan Tree with projecting roots, Honolulu, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS195, Ginger plants, Honolulu, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS196, Golden Cup, Honolulu, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS197, Monkeypod, Honolulu, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS198, Sugar Cane seedling at a Sugar station, Honolulu, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS199, Sugar Cane seedling at a Sugar station, Honolulu, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS200, Sugar Cane seedling at a Sugar station, Honolulu, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS200, Sugar Cane seedling at a Sugar station, Honolulu, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS201, Workers planting Sugar Cane seedling at a Sugar station, Honolulu, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS202, Sugar Cane seedling at a Sugar station, Honolulu, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS203, Sugar Cane seedling at a Sugar station, Honolulu, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS204, Taro, Honolulu, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS205, A Sugar station, Honolulu, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS206, Mitscherlich pots, Hawaiian Sugar Planters Association Experiment Station, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS207, A sunset, Honolulu, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS208, Honolulu, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS209, A beach in Honolulu, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS210, Falls near Honolulu, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS211, A fish pond, Honolulu, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS213, The docks at Honolulu, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS214, King Kamehameha statue, Honolulu, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS216, Aloha Tower, Honolulu, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS217, Inter Island Airways of Hawaii, USAM-33, Honolulu, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS218, S.S. Monterey docked at Honolulu, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS219, Royal Hawaiian Hotel, Honolulu, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS220, Woman making leis, Honolulu, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS221, Near Kahana Bay, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS222, Kailua Bay, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS223, Kaneohe, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS224, Fish ponds at Kaneohe Bay, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS225, Kaneohe Bay, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS226, Kaneohe Bay, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS227, Kaneohe Bay, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS228, Kaneohe, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS229, Kaneohe Bay, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS230, Koko Head, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS231, Koko Head and the road cut, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS232, Near Koko Head, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS233, Lighthouse Point at Waimanalo, Oahu, Hawaii AEP-HIS234, Nuuanu Valley
    - Idaho, AEP-IDS1, Pinus murrayana and Pseudotsuga, Caribou National Forest, Idaho AEP-IDS3, Picea engelmannii, Abies, and Pseudotsuga, Idaho AEP-IDS4, Pinus monticola, Abies, and Larix, Idaho AEP-IDS5, A virgin forest of Pinus monticola, Larix, and Tsuga, Idaho AEP-IDS6, A virgin forest of Pinus monticola, Thuja, Tsuga, and Larix, Idaho AEP-IDS7, A virgin forest of Pinus monticola, Thuja, Tsuga, and Abies, Idaho AEP-IDS8, A virgin forest of Pinus monticola, Idaho (Box CABINET 1, Folder Drawer 12)